White meat, such as chicken, may raise blood cholesterol levels as much as red meat
does. meat, such as chicken, may raise blood cholesterol levels as much as red meat
does. White meat, such as chicken, may raise blood cholesterol levels as much as red
meat does. This finding surprised researchers who admitted they didn't expect that
eating white meat would lead to higher blood cholesterol levels.
This finding surprised researchers who admitted they didn't expect that eating white
meat would lead to higher blood cholesterol levels.
In the study, researchers looked at 113 healthy people.
The participants ate three different diets.
These were a red meat diet, is primarily beef, a white meat diet, which is mostly
chicken and turkey, and a vegetarian protein diet.
These were a red meat diet, which is primarily beef, a white meat diet, which is
mostly chicken and turkey, and a vegetarian protein diet.
Each diet period was four weeks.
Between the diet periods, participants had a break, during which they ate their
regular foods. Each diet period was four weeks.
regular foods. In addition, participants had blood tests at the start and finish of
each new diet.
In addition, participants had blood tests at the start and finish of each new diet.
The results showed that